# Rajalakshmi Venkatramani

## Senior Executive Human Resources

**♀** Medical college road, Thanjavur, Tamil Nadu, India, (IN),

raji.sowmi17@gmail.com

+91 944-316-3416

in Rajalakshmi Venkatramani

#### About

Professional with over 10 years of progressive industry experience with a proven and consistent track record of professional achievements. Strong understanding and background in all phases of Recruitment Life Cycle. Strong relationship and team skills. Experience in managing a wide spectrum of HR activities encompassing Talent Acquisition, Induction, Employee Engagement Activity & Vendor Management.

## Experience

## **Inuson Private Limited**

November 2017 - Present

#### **Senior Executive Human Resources**

https://www.linkedin.com/company/28153219

Handling recruitment and new employee confirmation, induction and training. Handling leave maintenance, payroll, attendance and grievance handling. Handling performance appraisal, employee communication & exit formalities

#### **Tenpath**

**April 2012 - October 2017** 

## **HR Associate - Subject Matter Expert**

https://www.linkedin.com/company/3806681

Handling a team which includes 5-6 members, IT and non IT requirements in US Market. Getting potential candidates based on client's requirements.

Stand out Performer for 2 consecutive years
Organized numerous employee engagement programs
Organized employee health drive

#### Lifetime Careers

September 2011 - March 2012

#### **HR Recruiter**

https://www.linkedin.com/company/8311795

Handling recruitment, IT and non IT requirements in US Market. Getting potential candidates based on client's requirements.

#### Education

## **Bharathidasan University**

2009 - 2011

#### **MHRM**

## **Human Resources Management**

**☞** GPA: 7

Organizational Developement

personnel management

## **Bharath College of Science & Management**

2006 - 2009

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom

## **Business/Commerce, General**

Volunteer

## **KHS**

January 2012 - January 2013

## President - AIDS awareness club

Attended various AIDS awaremess camps aadudurai and throughout tamil nadu and organised a awaremess camp in thanjavur

Promoted as president in our school

**Awards** 

15 April 2007

Genral Proficiency in Mathamatics

**Bharath College** 

Secured first rank in mathamatics

## Skills

Recruiting	attendance management and Pa	ayroll Administration
Master	Master	Master
RCL		
Grievance Handling	Employee Training	Various Job Portals
Master	Master	Master
		naukri monster.com timesjob indeed linkedin

Data analytics

People management

## Languages

English	Tamil	Hindi
Professional Speaker	Native Speaker	intermediate

## Interests

Singing and Dancing Arts and Crafts